A Guide to the International Education Board records FA062
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1920-1960; 1
  - Fellowships in Agriculture, 4
    - Willy Dorner, 1928-1933 (Box 69, Folder 1153)
    - Marin Dracea, 1925-1930 (Box 69, Folder 1154)
      Reforestation.
    - Jean Dufernoy, 1926-1933 (Box 69, Folder 1155)
    - A. N. Dumitrescu, 1926 (Box 69, Folder 1156)
    - Hans Egner, 1925-1931 (Box 69, Folder 1157)
    - Conrad Elvehjem, 1928-1929 (Box 69, Folder 1158)
    - Sterling H. Emerson, 1925-1926 (Box 69, Folder 1159)
    - Otto Erdtman, 1929 (Box 69, Folder 1160)
      Geology.
    - Immanuel Fauser, 1924-1926 (Box 69, Folder 1161)
      Farm organization.
    - Daniel Feher, 1926-1934 (Box 69, Folder 1162)
    - Zdislaw Finik, 1924-1936 (Box 69, Folder 1163)
      Veterinary science.
    - G.F. Finlay, 1925 (Box 69, Folder 1164)
    - G. Fraenkel, 1929 (Box 69, Folder 1165)
    - Alan C. Fraser, 1925-1930 (Box 69, Folder 1166)
    - Walter Frei, 1926 (Box 69, Folder 1167)
    - Albert Frey, 1925-1928 (Box 69, Folder 1168)
    - C. Fromageot, 1928 (Box 69, Folder 1169)
    - Basil Ganossis, 1926-1940 (Box 70, Folder 1170)
    - Grace Gilchrist, 1924-1925 (Box 70, Folder 1171)
    - Hans Glomme, 1925-1930 (Box 70, Folder 1172)
    - Olga Gloy, 1924-1927 (Box 70, Folder 1173)
    - Michailo Gradoyevitch, 1926 (Box 70, Folder 1174)
    - Alfred R. H. Gron, 1926-1927 (Box 70, Folder 1175)
    - Jean Guerillot, 1926 (Box 70, Folder 1176)
    - William Hagan, 1925-1926 (Box 70, Folder 1177)
    - Edward Handschin, 1926-1932 (Box 70, Folder 1178)
    - Richard Harnach, 1926-1929 (Box 70, Folder 1179)
    - C. H. Helm, 1925 (Box 70, Folder 1180)
    - Arthur Henry, 1925-1931 (Box 70, Folder 1181)
    - Dr. Herbert-Nilsson, 1925 (Box 70, Folder 1182)
    - Arnold Hindricks, 1924 (Box 70, Folder 1183)
    - Henry S. Holden, 1925-1926 (Box 70, Folder 1184)
    - Erwin Hopler, 1924-1931 (Box 70, Folder 1185)
    - Sven Horstadins, 1929-1931 (Box 71, Folder 1186)
      Experimental zoology.
    - George J. Hucker, 1925-1928 (Box 71, Folder 1187)
    - Holja Huik, 1926 (Box 71, Folder 1188)
    - Bela Husz, 1924-1930 (Box 71, Folder 1189)
    - Boris Ilieff, 1924-1930 (Box 71, Folder 1190)
      Rural engineering.
    - Yrja Ilvessalo, 1925-1926 (Box 71, Folder 1191)
    - W. L. Ilyn, 1924 (Box 71, Folder 1192)
    - Temelko Ivantchoff, 1924-1927 (Box 71, Folder 1193)
    - Hans Jenny, 1925-1935 (Box 71, Folder 1194)
    - Ejnar Jensen, 1926-1927 (Box 71, Folder 1195)
    - Hans Jensen, 1926-1932 (Box 71, Folder 1196)
      Soil microbiology.
    - Karl Johannsson, 1925-1937 (Box 71, Folder 1197)
    - Arnold Johnson, 1926-1931 (Box 71, Folder 1198)
    - Arnold Johnson - Report (Box 71, Folder 1199)
    - Kalle Jutila, 1925-1928 (Box 72, Folder 1200)
    - Alfred Kalnins, 1925-1932 (Box 72, Folder 1201)
      Soil bacteriology.
    - Socrate Kaloyereas, 1926-1936 (Box 72, Folder 1202)
      Canning.
    - Karl Kanep, 1925-1929 (Box 72, Folder 1203)
    - Assen Kantardjieff, 1926-1930 (Box 72, Folder 1204)
    - Georgie Karpechenko, 1929 (Box 72, Folder 1205)
    - David Karunakar, 1924-1926 (Box 72, Folder 1206)
    - Laura Kaufman, 1925-1926 (Box 72, Folder 1207)
      Morphology.
    - Frank Kern, 1924-1925 (Box 72, Folder 1208)
    - Charles Killian, 1928-1929 (Box 72, Folder 1209)
      Ecology.
    - Walo Koch, 1928 (Box 72, Folder 1211)
    - Karoly Kolbai, 1924-1925 (Box 72, Folder 1212)
    - Stefan Kopec, 1926-1927 (Box 72, Folder 1213)
    - Peeter Kopp, 1924-1926 (Box 72, Folder 1214)
    - Mirko Koric, 1925-1929 (Box 72, Folder 1215)
    - Jan Korinek, 1929-1930 (Box 72, Folder 1216)
    - A. M. Koroleff, 1924 (Box 72, Folder 1217)
    - Dontcho Kostoff, 1926-1929 (Box 72, Folder 1218)
    - Flex Dotowski, 1926-1930 (Box 72, Folder 1219)
    - Jaroslav Krizenecky, 1928-1929 (Box 72, Folder 1220)
    - Peter Krosby, 1926-1930 (Box 72, Folder 1221)
      Plant breeding.
    - Cyrill Kucera, 1925-1928 (Box 73, Folder 1222)
    - Ottakar Kukula, 1925 (Box 73, Folder 1223)
    - H. Kuttner, 1925 (Box 73, Folder 1224)
    - Victor Lathouwers, 1924-1929 (Box 73, Folder 1225)
    - Julian Leach, 1926-1935 (Box 73, Folder 1226)
    - Linwood Lee, 1927-1929 (Box 73, Folder 1227)
    - Elmar Lepik, 1926-1928 (Box 73, Folder 1228)
    - Stefan Lewicki, 1927-1930 (Box 73, Folder 1229)
    - Berthold Lichtenberger, 1924-1926 (Box 73, Folder 1230)
      Dairy marketing.
    - Kurt Liebscher, 1924-1925 (Box 73, Folder 1231)
    - Pierre Lilloff, 1924-1931 (Box 73, Folder 1232)
      Pomology.
    - Karl Link, 1924-1938 (Box 73, Folder 1233)
      Carbohydrate chemistry.
    - Karl Link, 1924-1938 (Box 73, Folder 1234)
    - Anton List, 1924-1931 (Box 73, Folder 1235)
    - Jaan Magi, 1924-1938 (Box 74, Folder 1236)
      Stock breeding.
    - Kurt Maiwald, 1925-1940 (Box 74, Folder 1237)
    - Kurt Maiwald, 1925-1940 (Box 74, Folder 1238)
    - Edmond Malinowski, 1925-1933 (Box 74, Folder 1239)
    - Theodor Marchlewski, 1924-1927 (Box 74, Folder 1240)
    - Alma Martin, 1926-1927 (Box 74, Folder 1241)
      Home economics.
    - Audrei Mathiesen, 1924-1931 (Box 74, Folder 1242)
    - Armando Maugini, 1925-1927 (Box 74, Folder 1243)
      Dry farming.
    - L. A. Maynard, 1927-1935 (Box 74, Folder 1244)
    - Barbara McClintock, 1928 (Box 74, Folder 1245)
    - Elias Melin, 1926-1927 (Box 74, Folder 1246)
    - Jaan Mets, 1926-1931 (Box 74, Folder 1247)
    - Olavi Meurmann, 1927-1932 (Box 74, Folder 1248)
    - Ludwig Meyer, 1926-1930 (Box 75, Folder 1249)
      Soil nutrition.
    - Thaddaeus Miecznski, 1924-1928 (Box 75, Folder 1250)
    - Josef Mikulowski-Pomarski, 1924-1928 (Box 75, Folder 1251)
      Agricultural education.
    - John Mocsy, 1926-1927 (Box 75, Folder 1252)
    - George G. Moe, 1926-1929 (Box 75, Folder 1253)
      Agronomy.
    - Hans Nachtsheim, 1925-1927 (Box 75, Folder 1254)
    - Nichael Navashin, 1925-1929 (Box 75, Folder 1255)
    - Bernard Nebel, 1926-1928 (Box 75, Folder 1256)
    - Ethel Nightingale, 1924-1931 (Box 75, Folder 1257)
    - Ethel Nightingale, 1924-1931 (Box 75, Folder 1258)
    - Stefan Nikolic, 1925-1927 (Box 76, Folder 1259)
    - Gunnar Nilsson-Leissner, 1925-1936 (Box 76, Folder 1260)
    - Anton Nommik, 1924-1938 (Box 76, Folder 1261)
    - F. F. Nord, 1925-1927 (Box 76, Folder 1262)
    - Frank Novak, 1924-1925 (Box 76, Folder 1263)
    - Henry Oberhansley, 1924 (Box 76, Folder 1264)
    - Mikkel Odelien, 1926-1927 (Box 76, Folder 1265)
    - Ernst Oehler, 1927-1930 (Box 76, Folder 1266)
    - Albert Ogrizek, 1925-1936 (Box 76, Folder 1267)
    - Fridtjob Okland, 1924-1935 (Box 76, Folder 1268)
    - Gustar Oldenburg, 1924-1927 (Box 76, Folder 1269)
    - Paul Oreshkoff, 1928 (Box 76, Folder 1270)
    - L. Palmans, 1924-1927 (Box 77, Folder 1271)
      Limilogy.
    - John H. Parker, 1925-1928 (Box 77, Folder 1272)
      Cereal breeding.
    - Georg Paspaleff, 1925-1936 (Box 77, Folder 1273)
    - Jaroslaw Peklo, 1924-1931 (Box 77, Folder 1274)
    - Branko Peshitch, 1926 (Box 77, Folder 1275)
    - V. A. Pesola, 1926-1934 (Box 77, Folder 1276)
    - Beniamino Peyronel, 1925-1926 (Box 77, Folder 1277)
    - Otto Philipp, 1924-1925 (Box 77, Folder 1278)
    - Mihkel Pill, 1924-1931 (Box 77, Folder 1279)
    - John B. Platon, 1926-1931 (Box 77, Folder 1280)
    - Theodor Pool, 1925-1926 (Box 78, Folder 1281)
    - Ugo Pratolongo, 1924-1937 (Box 78, Folder 1282)
    - Heinrich Prell, 1925-1927 (Box 78, Folder 1283)
    - Emil Pribyl, 1926-1931 (Box 78, Folder 1284)
    - Gabriel Proytchoff, 1924-1929 (Box 78, Folder 1285)
    - Eduardo Quisumbing, 1925-1926 (Box 78, Folder 1286)
    - Lowell F. Randolph, 1926-1929 (Box 78, Folder 1287)
    - Hans Reihm, 1926-1928 (Box 78, Folder 1288)
      Soil chemistry.
    - Albert Riker, 1925-1932 (Box 78, Folder 1289)
      Plant bacteriology.
    - Alfred Rinne, 1928 (Box 78, Folder 1290)
    - William Roach, 1926-1927 (Box 78, Folder 1291)
    - Juan Rodriguez-Sardina, 1924-1926 (Box 78, Folder 1292)
    - Anastasie Rohizky, 1925-1927 (Box 78, Folder 1293)
    - Mikelis Rolle, 1926-1927 (Box 78, Folder 1294)
    - L. G. Rommel, 1925-1935 (Box 78, Folder 1295)
      Microbiology.
    - Kazimierz Rouppert, 1925-1930 (Box 78, Folder 1296)
    - Kirill Rudakov, 1926-1927 (Box 79, Folder 1297)
    - Wilfred Sadler, 1925-1929 (Box 79, Folder 1298)
    - Giulio Savastano, 1925-1933 (Box 79, Folder 1299)
    - Emil Scherf, 1924-1934 (Box 79, Folder 1300)
      Colloidal chemistry.
    - Stefan Schmidt, 1926-1928 (Box 79, Folder 1301)
    - George Scott-Blair, 1929 (Box 79, Folder 1302)
    - Tsunghan Shen, 1925-1929 (Box 79, Folder 1303)
    - Knut Skinnemoen, 1926-1927 (Box 79, Folder 1304)
    - Vladimir Skoric, 1925-1936 (Box 79, Folder 1305)
    - Elvira Smeyers, 1924-1929 (Box 79, Folder 1306)
    - Ladislav Smolik, 1926-1930 (Box 79, Folder 1307)
    - Stanislaw Smrecznski, 1928 (Box 79, Folder 1308)
    - Stepan Soudek, 1925-1929 (Box 79, Folder 1309)
    - Otto Spottel, 1927 (Box 80, Folder 1310)
    - Francis Staff, 1924-1931 (Box 80, Folder 1311)
    - Lars Stahl, 1926-1934 (Box 80, Folder 1312)
      Seed testing.
    - Martin G. Stalfelt, 1927-1929 (Box 80, Folder 1313)
    - Frederick C. Steward, 1927-1929 (Box 80, Folder 1314)
    - Vintila Stinghie, 1926 (Box 80, Folder 1315)
    - Erling Styri, 1925-1926 (Box 80, Folder 1316)
    - Olaf Tanem, 1926-1932 (Box 80, Folder 1317)
    - Alois Taviar, 1925-1936 (Box 80, Folder 1318)
    - Karl Tedin, 1925-1938 (Box 80, Folder 1319)
    - Hans Theiler, 1926-1927 (Box 80, Folder 1320)
    - William H. Thorpe, 1926-1937 (Box 80, Folder 1321)
    - S. R. Todorovic, 1924-1925 (Box 80, Folder 1322)
    - Ambrojioke Tomasi, 1928-1930 (Box 80, Folder 1323)
      Dairy chemistry.
    - Charles Tomlinson, 1925-1927 (Box 80, Folder 1324)
      To administer only.
    - Alan Treolar, 1927-1960 (Box 81, Folder 1325)
      Cereal chemistry.
    - Bernard Trouvelot, 1927-1939 (Box 81, Folder 1326)
    - Pauli Tuorila, 1925-1930 (Box 81, Folder 1327)
    - Gate Turesson, 1926-1928 (Box 81, Folder 1328)
    - Vladimir Tymoshenko, 1925-1929 (Box 81, Folder 1329)
    - Jaak Umarik, 1924-1930 (Box 81, Folder 1330)
      Vocational education.
    - Thomas Vacek, 1925-1934 (Box 81, Folder 1331)
    - Stefan Vagi, 1926 (Box 81, Folder 1332)
    - Henrick van der Lek, 1925-1931 (Box 81, Folder 1333)
      Microtome technique.
    - Jikke van der Meer, 1926-1932 (Box 81, Folder 1334)
    - Germain Verplancke, 1926-1932 (Box 81, Folder 1335)
    - Johan Von Monroy, 1925-1938 (Box 81, Folder 1336)
    - Harry Waren, 1929 (Box 81, Folder 1337)
    - Georg Weininger, 1924-1925 (Box 81, Folder 1338)
    - S. J. Wellensick, 1926-1928 (Box 81, Folder 1339)
    - Melchoir Westhues, 1925-1931 (Box 82, Folder 1340)
    - Haakon Wexelsen, 1925-1928 (Box 82, Folder 1341)
    - J. J. Willaman, 1926-1928 (Box 82, Folder 1342)
      Plant biochemistry.
    - Thomas Zacharieff, 1924-1931 (Box 82, Folder 1343)
    - Francis Zucker, 1926-1935 (Box 82, Folder 1344)
    - Fellowships in Agriculture - Far East, 1925-1927 (Box 82, Folder 1345)
    - Kazuo Goton, 1925-1927 (Box 82, Folder 1346)
    - Yoshitaka Imai, 1925-1929 (Box 82, Folder 1347)
    - Takeo Matsuda, 1925-1928 (Box 82, Folder 1348)
    - Nemesio Mendiola, 1926-1929 (Box 82, Folder 1349)
    - Takajiro Mori, 1925-1930 (Box 82, Folder 1350)
    - Ivan Phipps, 1925-1929 (Box 83, Folder 1351)
    - Hatsutaro Tanahashi, 1925-1928 (Box 83, Folder 1352)
    - Seuchi Tobata, 1925-1927 (Box 83, Folder 1353)
    - A. W. Turner, 1926-1934 (Box 83, Folder 1354)
    - H. C. Weekes, 1929 (Box 83, Folder 1355)
    - Nobumasa Yogi, 1925-1927 (Box 83, Folder 1356)
    - Fellowships By Country - I. E. B. Fellowships, 1924-1928 (Box 83, Folder 1357)
      Working copy.
    - Fellowships By Country - I. E. B. Fellowships, 1924-1928 (Box 83, Folder 1358)
- Finances, 1923-1964; 2
  This series contains ledgers, journals, cashbooks, audits and reports and appropriations accounts.
  - Audits, 1924-1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Audits, 1924-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Finance Committee Minutes, 1925-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Frants P. Lund Ledger, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Statements to the Treasurer, 1926-1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1924-1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1924-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1924-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Trial Balance, 1925-1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Trial Balance, 1925-1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Trial Balance, 1925-1939 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Appropriations, February 1923-July 1925 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Appropriations, May 1925-June 1926 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Appropriations, May 1926-June 1927 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Appropriations, May 1927-June 1928 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Appropriations, July 1928-1938 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - General Ledger (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Ledger Accounts #1 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Ledger Accounts #2 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Ledger Accounts #3 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Statements, 1923-1938 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cash Book #1, 1923-February 1926 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Cash Book #2, March 1926-July 1931 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Cash Book #3, July 1931-1938 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Trial Balance, 1928-1938 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Journal Entries, 1925-1938 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Journal No. 1, February 1923-March 1926 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Journal No. 2, April 1926-June 1938 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Account Book, 1925-1934 (Box 10A, Folder 29)
  - International Education Board and General Education Board Securities Ledger #2, 1927-1964 (Box 10B, Folder 30)
- Minutes, Dockets, Annual Reports, 1923-1938; 3
  - Annual Report, 1923-June 1924 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Research Fellowships Granted, 1924-June 1928 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Fellowship Dockets - Paris Office, 1928-1930 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, February 3, 1923-July 11, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, July 31, 1924-May 29, 1925 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, February 3, 1923-July 11, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, July 31, 1924-May 29, 1925 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, June 1925-November 1925 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, November 1926-May 1928 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, May 1928-December 1930 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, January 1931-December 1938 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - International Education Board Minutes Index, 4 box(es) 4x6x12 inches each.
    The index includes entries for personal names and organizations, not subject terms or geographic places. Citations to the IEB's minutes appear as dates on the left edge of the cards, and page numbers on the right.
    The index is arranged alphabetically.
    - A - Fellowships in Science (Box 35A)
    - Fellowships in Science - L (Box 35B)
    - M - S (Box 35C)
    - T - Z (Box 35D)
  - Dockets, 1923-1924 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Dockets, January-July 1925 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Dockets, July 1925-January 1926 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Dockets, January-July 1926 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Dockets, October-December 1926 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Dockets, February-June 1927 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Dockets, October-December 1927 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Dockets, February-June 1928 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Dockets, September 1928-April 1931 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Dockets, October 1931-December 1938 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Fellowship Book, 1925-1931 (Box 37A, Folder 24)
    Includes sections for Science, National Research Council, and Traveling Professors.
  - Fellowship Book (Box 37B)
- International Education Board photographs, 1910-1931; 1023; 0.5 Cubic Feet; 13 folders; 145 prints.
  The International Education Board was incorporated January 12, 1923, in the state of Virginia. Its purpose was to promote education, institutional or otherwise, throughout the world and as such was a complement to the General Education Board which functioned in the United States. Wickliffe Rose resigned from the International Health Board in 1923 to become director of both boards. At his retirement in 1928, the International Education Board discontinued its active program.
  The International Education Board promoted the advancement of education through grants to universities and through a multitude of fellowships to individuals. It sponsored the strengthening of disciplines with such grants as those to develop Mount Palomar and traveling professorships and fellowships. While the main fields of the board were the physical and natural sciences and agriculture, some appropriations were made in the humanities and social sciences as to the American Academy in Rome, the Oriental Institute in Chicago and the New York State Colonization Society for the Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia.
  The Board terminated its activities on December 31, 1938.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Collection is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
  Photographs
  - California Institute of Technology Observatory, 1910-1929; Mounted on board, captions on back, some edge fading and yellowing; 8 prints (Box 9, Folder 78)
    Telescopes, building exteriors, spectography, spiral nebulas, astronomy.
  - Denmark - Farm Work Demonstration, 1924-1926; Mounted on board, captions on back, some yellowing, fading; 30 prints (Box 9, Folder 79)
    Farns, agriculture, clubs, children.
  - Finland - Boys and Girls Club Work, Mounted on board, captions on back, some silvering, yellowing, fading; 35 prints (Box 9, Folder 80)
    Children, clubs, agriculture, farming, produce.
  - France - Aid to Marine Biological Research, 1929 November; 4 prints (Box 9, Folder 81)
    Villafranche, France. Dr. Tregouboff, Dr. Metalnikov, Dr. Davidoff.
    Separated Materials note
    Removed from Box 34, Folder 481.
  - Harvard College Observatory, 1925; Mounted on board, captions on back, most yellowing, fading; 7 prints (Box 9, Folder 82)
    Star clusters; astronomy; Arequipa, Peru.
  - Holland - Agricultural University, Mounted on board, caption on back; 1 print (Box 9, Folder 83)
    Schools, agriculture.
  - Hungary - Hungarian Village Association, 1924; Mounted on board, captions on back, yellowing, silvering; 6 prints (Box 9, Folder 84)
    Agriculture, farming, crafts, cultural lifestyles.
  - Japan - Biological Institute, Tohoku, Mounted on board, captions on back, some fading; 6 prints (Box 9, Folder 85)
    Schools, buildings.
  - Italy - American Academy in Rome, 1926-1929; Mounted on board, captions on back,; 2 prints (Box 9, Folder 86)
    Schools, buildings, dedication plaques.
  - Italy - Naples Zoological Station, 1926; Mounted on board, captions on back, some fading; 3 prints (Box 9, Folder 87)
    Schools, dedication plaques.
  - Spain - Institute of Physics and Chemistry, Madrid, circa 1930; Mounted on board, captions on back, slight fading; 6 prints (Box 9, Folder 88)
    Schools, machinery, equipment, laboratories, libraries.
  - Sweden - Boys and Girls Club Work, 1924-1927; Mounted on board, captions on back, some fading, silvering; 27 prints (Box 10, Folder 89)
    Agriculture, farming, children, produce.
  - Sweden - University of Upsala Physical Chemistry Laboratory, 1931; Mounted on board, captions on back; 9 prints (Box 10, Folder 90)
    Machinery, equipment, laboratories, schools.